All right. To start using the SageMaker,
好的要开始使用 SageMaker
the first thing we're going to need to do is set up a notebook instance.
首先需要设置一个 notebook 实例
To do that, we need to sign into the AWS console, which I have done here,
我们需要登录 AWS 控制台 我已经登录了
and then scroll down and underneath Machine Learning,
然后向下滚动到 Machine Learning 部分
we want to click on Amazon SageMaker.
点击下方的 Amazon SageMaker
This will open up the SageMaker dashboard.
这样就会打开 SageMaker Dashboard
From here on the left-hand side,
在左侧
we want to click on notebook instances.
点击 Notebook instances
As you can see, I don't have any set-up currently.
我还没有设置任何 Notebook 实例
To make a new one, we click on this orange button in the top right corner
点击右上角的橘色按钮
that says Create Notebook instance.
“Create notebook instance”
Most of these settings are fine the way they are.
大部分设置都不用改动
However, we do need to name our notebook instance.
但是 我们需要命名 notebook 实例
I'm going to call mine deployment-notebook.
我将其称为 deployment-notebook
We also need to make sure to set a role.
还需要设置一个角色
A role acts like a security certificate,
角色就像一个安全证书
letting Amazon know what other resources are notebook we'll have access to.
告诉 Amazon 我们的 notebook 可以访问哪些其他资源
We need to make sure that we allow our notebook access to S3.
我们需要确保我们的 notebook 可以访问 S3
To do that, we click on this drop-down and select Create a new role.
所以点击这个下拉列表并选择“Create a new role”
The default selections will be perfectly fine.
默认设置就可以了
The most important line is the second one here that says
最重要的是第二个复选框
any S3 bucket with SageMaker in the name can be accessed by our notebook.
它指出名称中有 SageMaker 的任何 S3 存储桶都可以访问我们的 notebook
Since there are no additional buckets,
因为我们的 notebook 没有其他可以访问的存储桶
we want to have our notebook access we'll select None here.
所以这里选择“None”
A little later on, we'll talk about what S3 is.
稍后我会讲解什么是 S3
But, for now, just think of it as a place to store data,
暂时将其看作可以存储数据的位置
like training data, or maybe a trained model.
例如训练数据或训练的模型
Once we've done this, we click on Create role.
设置完毕后 点击“Create role”
The role has now been created and automatically assigned to our notebook instance.
该角色已创建并自动分配给我们的 notebook 实例
To finish it up, we just scroll down to the bottom and click on Create notebook instance.
为了完成设置 我们需要滚动到底部并点击“Create notebook instance”
The status of our notebook instance is now pending,
notebook 实例的状态现在是“pending”
which means that Amazon is working away in the background to set everything up.
表示 Amazon 正在后台进行设置
At this point, we just need to wait and
此刻我们只需等待
Amazon has finished setting up our notebook instance.
现在 Amazon 设置好 notebook 实例了
If we look under the status column now,
状态列下方
it says that our notebook instance is inService,
显示为“InService”
which means that it's running.
表示 notebook 正在运行
Now, it's important to note that the default behavior
需要注意的是 默认情况下
is for a notebook to begin running once you've created it.
notebook 创建好后就会开始运行
It's important to know that because the cost of
一定要知道这一点
a notebook instance is based on the length of time that it's running.
因为 notebook 实例按照运行时长计费
So, if you aren't going to be using your notebook,
如果你不使用 notebook
make sure to stop it and then start it again later.
一定要停止它并稍后再启动